<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Calliope mini v.2 (BETA)</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_editors">Editors</string>
    <string name="title_help">Help</string>

    <string name="title_location_permission">LOCATION PERMISSION REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="title_bluetooth_permission">BLUETOOTH PERMISSION REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="info_location_permission">From Android 6.0 Marshmallow onwards the application requires Location permission in order to scan for Bluetooth devices.
        \n\nThis is because Bluetooth may be used to determine the phone\'s and user\'s location, <b>mini</b> will not use this information in any way.</string>
    <string name="info_bluetooth_permission">To use Bluetooth features to communicate APP with your <b>mini</b> you must granted several permissions.</string>

    <string name="settings_btn_permission">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_btn_permission">Grant permission</string>

    <string name="title_make_code">MakeCode</string>
    <string name="title_roberta">Open Roberta Lab</string>
    <string name="title_library">Preinstalled Programs</string>
    <string name="title_scripts">Your scripts</string>
    <string name="info_make_code">Microsoft MakeCode is a free, open source platform for creating engaging computer science learning experiences that support a progression path into real-world programming.</string>
    <string name="info_roberta">The Open Roberta Lab is a cloud-based integrated programming environment that enables children and adolescents to program easily different robot/microcontroller systems.</string>
    <string name="info_library">Here you find the original programs, to change or reload.</string>
    <string name="info_scripts">Here is you scripts.</string>

    <string name="title_welcome">LET\'S GO</string>
    <string name="info_welcome">On this page you will learn how to get the Calliope mini up and running step by step. The first step shows you how to connect the Calliope mini correctly to the power supply.</string>

    <string name="title_battery">CONNECT</string>
    <string name="info_battery"><![CDATA[
    Before you can start, the Calliope mini must be powered.
    <br/>
    <br/>1. fill the battery compartment with two batteries of type <b>AAA</b>. Make sure that the batteries are aligned correctly.
    <br/>
    <br/>2. take the battery block provided and carefully insert the small, <b>white plastic end (JST connector)</b> into the battery connector attached to the Calliope mini.
    <br/>
    <br/>Make sure that the closed end of the plug is at the top with the raised part in the middle. If the cable connector fits easily into the battery connector on the board, it is correct.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="title_demo">DEMO SEQUENCE</string>
    <string name="info_demo"><![CDATA[
    Meet the Calliope mini. The Calliope mini will show you on the display which input you should make.
    <br/>
    <br/>1. press the button <b>A</b>.
    <br/>2. press the button <b>B</b>.
    <br/>3. press the keys <b>A+B</b> simultaneously.
    <br/>4. The position sensor - shake the Calliope mini.
    <br/>5. Ready!
    ]]></string>

    <string name="info_app"><![CDATA[
    <b>Hello and welcome to the Calliope mini app!</b>
    <br/>
    <br/>By using this app you can connect, code and flash programs to your <b>Calliope mini</b> via Bluetooth.
    <br/>
    <br/>You can find inspiring and fun projects at the Calliope website at <a href="https://calliope.cc">calliope.cc</a>!
    <br/>
    <br/>Have fun!
    <br/>
    <br/>Calliope gGmbH
    <br/>Raumerstrasse 11
    <br/>10437 Berlin
    <br/>Germany
    <br/>E-Mail: <a href="mailto:info@calliope.cc">info@calliope.cc</a>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="welcome">welcome</string>
</resources>