<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Calliope mini</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_coding">Editors and Programs</string>
    <string name="title_help">Help</string>

    <string name="title_location_permission">LOCATION PERMISSION REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="title_bluetooth_permission">BLUETOOTH PERMISSION REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="info_location_permission">From Android 6.0 Marshmallow onwards the application requires Location permission in order to scan for Bluetooth devices.
        \n\nThis is because Bluetooth may be used to determine the phone\'s and user\'s location. <b>mini</b> will not use this information in any way.</string>
    <string name="info_bluetooth_permission">To use Bluetooth features to communicate APP with your <b>mini</b> you must granted several permissions.</string>

    <string name="settings_btn_permission">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_btn_permission">Grant permission</string>

    <string name="title_make_code">MakeCode</string>
    <string name="title_roberta">Open Roberta Lab</string>
    <string name="title_library">Preinstalled Programs</string>
    <string name="info_make_code">Microsoft MakeCode is a free, open source platform for creating engaging computer science learning experiences that support a progression path into real-world programming.</string>
    <string name="info_roberta">The Open Roberta Lab is a cloud-based integrated programming environment that enables children and adolescents to program easily different robot/microcontroller systems.</string>
    <string name="info_library">Here you find the original programs, to change or reload.</string>

    <string name="info_app"><![CDATA[
    <b>Hello and welcome to the Calliope mini app!</b>
    <br/>
    <br/>By using this app you can connect, code and flash programs to your <b>Calliope mini</b> via Bluetooth.
    <br/>
    <br/>You can find inspiring and fun projects at the Calliope website at <a href="https://calliope.cc">calliope.cc</a>!
    <br/>
    <br/>Have fun!
    <br/>
    <br/>Calliope gGmbH
    <br/>Raumerstrasse 11
    <br/>10437 Berlin
    <br/>Germany
    <br/>E-Mail: <a href="mailto:info@calliope.cc">info@calliope.cc</a>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="insert_battery_00">1. fill the battery compartment with two batteries of type AAA. Make sure that the batteries are aligned correctly.</string>
    <string name="insert_battery_01">2. take the battery block provided and carefully insert the small, white plastic end (JST connector) into the battery connector attached to the Calliope mini.</string>
    <string name="welcome">welcome</string>
</resources>